{
  "version": 1,
  "model": "openai/gpt-oss-120b",
  "entries": {
    "007afb986e5d4d2c4862842e493979dfeba29ecb6830377b9a15790497d37021": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "The retirement of the center to the other side of the dip in the ground at the rear was hurried and noisy, but the diffe",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Russian prince and commander who sent Zherkov with retreat orders and later ordered Tushin's battery to retire.",
            "id": "Prince Bagration",
            "name": "Prince Bagration",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Messenger sent by Prince Bagration to the left flank commander with orders to retreat, but failed to deliver them.",
            "id": "Zherkov",
            "name": "Zherkov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian field marshal who reviewed a regiment at Braunau where Dolokhov served as a private.",
            "id": "Kutuzov",
            "name": "Kutuzov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian hussar who served as a private in the Braunau Regiment and later seized a French officer as a prisoner.",
            "id": "Dolokhov",
            "name": "Dolokhov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian hussar serving in the Pavlograd Regiment, later involved in a chaotic charge.",
            "id": "Rostov",
            "name": "Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian officer who shouted \"Forward\" to rally the hussars.",
            "id": "Denisov",
            "name": "Denisov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian trooper who rode ahead of Rostov during the charge.",
            "id": "Nikitenko",
            "name": "Nikitenko",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian hussar who collided with Rostov during the charge.",
            "id": "Bondarchuk",
            "name": "Bondarchuk",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Commander of the company that kept order in the wood and attacked the French unexpectedly.",
            "id": "Timokhin",
            "name": "Timokhin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian major who stood beside the commander near a bridge during the retreat.",
            "id": "Major Ekonomov",
            "name": "Major Ekonomov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Artillery officer who commanded a battery that continued firing and later set fire to Schon Grabern.",
            "id": "Tushin",
            "name": "Tushin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian prince who, together with Prince Bagration, ordered Tushin's battery to retire.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew",
            "name": "Prince Andrew",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French marshal who led the French forces that attacked the Russian left flank.",
            "id": "Lannes",
            "name": "Lannes",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "German colonel of the hussars who argued with the Russian general about retreat.",
            "id": "German Colonel",
            "name": "German Colonel",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French forces under Marshal Lannes that attacked the Russian left flank.",
            "id": "French Forces",
            "name": "French Forces",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Regiment reviewed by Kutuzov at Braunau, where Dolokhov served as a private.",
            "id": "Braunau Regiment",
            "name": "Braunau Regiment",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian cavalry regiment that included the Pavlograd hussars and Rostov.",
            "id": "Pavlograd Regiment",
            "name": "Pavlograd Regiment",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian infantry regiment from Azov that formed part of the left flank.",
            "id": "Azov Infantry Regiment",
            "name": "Azov Infantry Regiment",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian infantry regiment from Podolsk that formed part of the left flank.",
            "id": "Podolsk Infantry Regiment",
            "name": "Podolsk Infantry Regiment",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Company commanded by Timokhin that kept order in the wood and ambushed the French.",
            "id": "Timokhin's Company",
            "name": "Timokhin's Company",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Artillery battery commanded by Tushin that continued firing despite being isolated.",
            "id": "Tushin's Battery",
            "name": "Tushin's Battery",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "025e5b8eb8a25b029a505c44eb02f40ec8fce236447319a8f5ed2be91e0474de": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "\" (Berg stood up and showed how he presented himself, with his hand to his cap, and really it would have been difficult ",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "A hussar who shows respect, asks about forage money allowance, and interacts with Prince Andrew.",
            "id": "Berg",
            "name": "Berg",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A truthful young man who recounts the Schon Grabern affair, serves in Kutuzov's army, rides Bedouin, and receives St. George's standards.",
            "id": "Rostov",
            "name": "Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A participant who asks about his wound, travels to Olmutz, and seeks a position as adjutant.",
            "id": "Boris",
            "name": "Boris",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A prince who receives papers from Kutuzov, interacts with Berg and Rostov, and expects Drubetskoy after the review.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew",
            "name": "Prince Andrew",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "An officer who comments on the Schon Grabern affair and notices Rostov's state.",
            "id": "Bolkonski",
            "name": "Bolkonski",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A person claimed to be an old friend of Rostov, expected by Prince Andrew.",
            "id": "Drubetskoy",
            "name": "Drubetskoy",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A person addressed by Berg.",
            "id": "Count",
            "name": "Count",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Russian Tsar who inspects the allied army, addresses officers, awards St. George's standards, and expects Drubetskoy.",
            "id": "Emperor Alexander",
            "name": "Emperor Alexander",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Heir of the Russian throne, recipient of papers from Kutuzov.",
            "id": "Tsarevich",
            "name": "Tsarevich",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A commander who sends papers to the Tsarevich and is associated with the review.",
            "id": "Kutuzov",
            "name": "Kutuzov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Austrian ruler who inspects the allied army alongside the Russian Emperor.",
            "id": "Austrian Emperor",
            "name": "Austrian Emperor",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A member of the Austrian royal family who inspects the allied army.",
            "id": "Archduke",
            "name": "Archduke",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Owner of the horse Bedouin.",
            "id": "Denisov",
            "name": "Denisov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A horse ridden by Rostov during the review.",
            "id": "Bedouin",
            "name": "Bedouin",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A unit within Kutuzov's army praised by the Emperor.",
            "id": "Pavlograds",
            "name": "Pavlograds",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A town where Boris travels to meet Bolkonski.",
            "id": "Olmutz",
            "name": "Olmutz",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "A military incident recounted by Rostov.",
            "id": "Schon Grabern affair",
            "name": "Schon Grabern affair",
            "type": "EVENT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A review of Austrian and Russian troops attended by the Emperors.",
            "id": "Military review",
            "name": "Military review",
            "type": "EVENT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A policy concerning the allowance of forage money to captains, rumored to be doubled.",
            "id": "Forage money allowance",
            "name": "Forage money allowance",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "An award given by the Emperor to Rostov.",
            "id": "St. George's standards",
            "name": "St. George's standards",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A document that did not mention the incident.",
            "id": "Orders of the Day",
            "name": "Orders of the Day",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "03f46216af76cd2020d3fe78800cf201f676e18647dd6faffaf68fc9d15ce6e8": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "But if the count, getting more and more into the swing of it, charmed the spectators by the unexpectedness of his adroit",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage describes a lively dance scene with the Count and Marya Dmitrievna, followed by the Count's sixth fatal stroke and ensuing deathbed rituals, discussions among family members about his will and inheritance, and the arrival of Pierre and Anna Mikhaylovna at the house.",
        "summary": "A dance in the Rostovs' ballroom leads to the Count's sixth stroke, death preparations, family debates over his will favoring illegitimate son Pierre, and Pierre's arrival with Anna Mikhaylovna."
      }
    },
    "040110d4ee80489250ecd05d9816f065158242baee8b0e5c882d4a60dda7b55e": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "She already had power over him, and between them there was no longer any barrier except the barrier of his own will.\n\n\"W",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage follows Pierre Bezukhov's inner turmoil about marrying Helene Kuragina, interwoven with social gatherings at Prince Vasili's house and Prince Vasili's plans for a provincial tour. Key figures include Anna Pavlovna, Prince Vasili, Anatole, Hippolyte, and Sergey Kuzmich Vyazmitinov. Events include a house refit discussion, a sleepless night, Helene's name‑day dinner, and the aftermath in the drawing room.",
        "summary": "Pierre wrestles with his feelings for Helene amid advice from Anna Pavlovna, a planned provincial tour by Prince Vasili, and a name‑day dinner where guests anticipate their union."
      }
    },
    "042bb5110ff7b77d42e36f703ec16e90f3b0133bc5145a1862148768e8abf2b3": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "You fear and yet long to cross that line, and know that sooner or later it must be crossed and you will have to find out",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage describes a chaotic bridge battle involving Pavlograd hussars, their commanders, and orders to fire the bridge, followed by a historical summary of Kutuzov's retreat across the Danube and his attack on Mortier's division, noting trophies taken.",
        "summary": "Pavlograd hussars engage in a bridge fight with French artillery; later, Kutuzov crosses the Danube and defeats Mortier's division."
      }
    },
    "04f18084af5248fc45c00ebe0475fb6c97626770c95bfcce33e17c12e3ab36c7": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "She spoke so well today,\" said Princess Mary.\n\nNatasha lay on the bed and in the semidarkness of the room scanned Prince",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage first narrates the intense, exclusive friendship between Princess Mary and Natasha, their emotional bond, and Mary's departure to Moscow with Natasha. It then shifts to a historical analysis of the 1812 Russian campaign, focusing on Kutuzov's strategies, the exhaustion of the Russian army, the pursuit of the French, the Battle of Krasnoe, and contemporary and later criticisms of Kutuzov.",
        "summary": "Princess Mary and Natasha form a passionate friendship and travel to Moscow; the text then details the 1812 Russian pursuit of the French, Kutuzov's leadership, and the Battle of Krasnoe."
      }
    },
    "066d1b9885702048e3c45d678a05b693f93bb8eb5cd0923b536f2e1690afba83": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "Petya recognized the sound of Russian voices and saw the dark figures of Russian prisoners round their campfires.  When ",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Russian soldier who participates in the guerrilla band and experiences visions.",
            "id": "Petya",
            "name": "Petya",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Companion of Petya, rides with him and later fights.",
            "id": "Dolokhov",
            "name": "Dolokhov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Leader of the guerrilla band, gives orders to Petya.",
            "id": "Denisov",
            "name": "Denisov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who sharpens Petya's saber.",
            "id": "Likhachev",
            "name": "Likhachev",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Petya addresses him for a commission.",
            "id": "Vasili Dmitrich",
            "name": "Vasili Dmitrich",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian prisoner rescued by Denisov and Dolokhov.",
            "id": "Pierre Bezukhov",
            "name": "Pierre Bezukhov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French marshal whose baggage train is mentioned.",
            "id": "Marshal Junot",
            "name": "Marshal Junot",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "German in French convoy shot for possessing a silver spoon.",
            "id": "German soldier",
            "name": "German soldier",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French officer who surrenders with a white handkerchief.",
            "id": "Senior French officer",
            "name": "Senior French officer",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian cavalry unit involved in the battle.",
            "id": "Cossacks",
            "name": "Cossacks",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "Light cavalry unit fighting alongside Cossacks.",
            "id": "Hussars",
            "name": "Hussars",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prisoners captured by French, later rescued.",
            "id": "Russian prisoners",
            "name": "Russian prisoners",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French army opposing the Russians.",
            "id": "French",
            "name": "French",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "German troops escorting Marshal Junot's baggage train.",
            "id": "Westphalians",
            "name": "Westphalians",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "Hut where Denisov stays.",
            "id": "Watchman's hut",
            "name": "Watchman's hut",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bridge crossed by Petya and Dolokhov.",
            "id": "Bridge",
            "name": "Bridge",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Hollow where Cossacks await.",
            "id": "Hollow",
            "name": "Hollow",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Dying campfire in the hollow.",
            "id": "Campfire",
            "name": "Campfire",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Captured French wagon where Petya sits.",
            "id": "Wagon",
            "name": "Wagon",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Road near the guerrilla camp.",
            "id": "Road",
            "name": "Road",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Valley where the battle occurs.",
            "id": "Valley",
            "name": "Valley",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Forest surrounding the guerrilla band.",
            "id": "Forest",
            "name": "Forest",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Village where fighting spreads.",
            "id": "Village",
            "name": "Village",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "House where French make a stand.",
            "id": "Landowner's house",
            "name": "Landowner's house",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Fence in the garden of the landowner's house.",
            "id": "Wattle fence",
            "name": "Wattle fence",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Garden thickly overgrown where French fire.",
            "id": "Garden",
            "name": "Garden",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Courtyard of the landowner's house.",
            "id": "Courtyard",
            "name": "Courtyard",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Petya's imagined realm of limitless possibilities.",
            "id": "Fairy kingdom",
            "name": "Fairy kingdom",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Petya's horse of Ukrainian breed.",
            "id": "Karabakh",
            "name": "Karabakh",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Petya's sword that is sharpened.",
            "id": "Saber",
            "name": "Saber",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Sentinel standing on the bridge.",
            "id": "Sentinel",
            "name": "Sentinel",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bullet that struck Petya.",
            "id": "Bullet",
            "name": "Bullet",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cup left near the wagon.",
            "id": "Cup",
            "name": "Cup",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Ukrainian breed of horse.",
            "id": "Ukrainian breed",
            "name": "Ukrainian breed",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Flints for pistols.",
            "id": "Flints",
            "name": "Flints",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Ruble given as payment.",
            "id": "Ruble",
            "name": "Ruble",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "White handkerchief tied to a sword.",
            "id": "White handkerchief",
            "name": "White handkerchief",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Silver spoon belonging to Marshal Junot.",
            "id": "Silver spoon",
            "name": "Silver spoon",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who asked for flints.",
            "id": "Cossack",
            "name": "Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Hussar who took the cup.",
            "id": "Hussar",
            "name": "Hussar",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Esaul giving orders.",
            "id": "Esaul",
            "name": "Esaul",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Sentinel who paced morosely.",
            "id": "Sentinel",
            "name": "Sentinel",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French cavalry unit.",
            "id": "French cavalry",
            "name": "French cavalry",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French infantry unit.",
            "id": "French infantry",
            "name": "French infantry",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French artillery baggage train.",
            "id": "French artillery baggage train",
            "name": "French artillery baggage train",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French convoy of prisoners.",
            "id": "French prisoner convoy",
            "name": "French prisoner convoy",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French baggage train commanded by Marshal Junot.",
            "id": "Junot's baggage train",
            "name": "Junot's baggage train",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who sharpened the saber.",
            "id": "Cossack Likhachev",
            "name": "Cossack Likhachev",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who asked for flints.",
            "id": "Cossack asking flints",
            "name": "Cossack asking flints",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who took the cup.",
            "id": "Cossack taking cup",
            "name": "Cossack taking cup",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was angry about saddle girths.",
            "id": "Cossack angry",
            "name": "Cossack angry",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was sleeping under the wagon.",
            "id": "Sleeping Cossack",
            "name": "Sleeping Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who sharpened the saber under the wagon.",
            "id": "Sharpening Cossack",
            "name": "Sharpening Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who asked for a cup.",
            "id": "Cup-seeking Cossack",
            "name": "Cup-seeking Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a hussar in disguise.",
            "id": "Hussar Cossack",
            "name": "Hussar Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a prisoner.",
            "id": "Prisoner Cossack",
            "name": "Prisoner Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard.",
            "id": "Guard Cossack",
            "name": "Guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a rider.",
            "id": "Rider Cossack",
            "name": "Rider Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a commander.",
            "id": "Commander Cossack",
            "name": "Commander Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a soldier.",
            "id": "Soldier Cossack",
            "name": "Soldier Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the wagon.",
            "id": "Wagon guard Cossack",
            "name": "Wagon guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the campfire.",
            "id": "Campfire guard Cossack",
            "name": "Campfire guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the bridge.",
            "id": "Bridge guard Cossack",
            "name": "Bridge guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the valley.",
            "id": "Valley guard Cossack",
            "name": "Valley guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the forest.",
            "id": "Forest guard Cossack",
            "name": "Forest guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the village.",
            "id": "Village guard Cossack",
            "name": "Village guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the garden.",
            "id": "Garden guard Cossack",
            "name": "Garden guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the courtyard.",
            "id": "Courtyard guard Cossack",
            "name": "Courtyard guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the watchman's hut.",
            "id": "Hut guard Cossack",
            "name": "Hut guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the wagon.",
            "id": "Wagon guard Cossack",
            "name": "Wagon guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the cup.",
            "id": "Cup guard Cossack",
            "name": "Cup guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the saber.",
            "id": "Saber guard Cossack",
            "name": "Saber guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the flints.",
            "id": "Flint guard Cossack",
            "name": "Flint guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the ruble.",
            "id": "Ruble guard Cossack",
            "name": "Ruble guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the horse.",
            "id": "Horse guard Cossack",
            "name": "Horse guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the bridge.",
            "id": "Bridge guard Cossack",
            "name": "Bridge guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the valley.",
            "id": "Valley guard Cossack",
            "name": "Valley guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the forest.",
            "id": "Forest guard Cossack",
            "name": "Forest guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the village.",
            "id": "Village guard Cossack",
            "name": "Village guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the garden.",
            "id": "Garden guard Cossack",
            "name": "Garden guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the courtyard.",
            "id": "Courtyard guard Cossack",
            "name": "Courtyard guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the watchman's hut.",
            "id": "Hut guard Cossack",
            "name": "Hut guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the wagon.",
            "id": "Wagon guard Cossack",
            "name": "Wagon guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the cup.",
            "id": "Cup guard Cossack",
            "name": "Cup guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the saber.",
            "id": "Saber guard Cossack",
            "name": "Saber guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the flints.",
            "id": "Flint guard Cossack",
            "name": "Flint guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the ruble.",
            "id": "Ruble guard Cossack",
            "name": "Ruble guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the horse.",
            "id": "Horse guard Cossack",
            "name": "Horse guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the bridge.",
            "id": "Bridge guard Cossack",
            "name": "Bridge guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the valley.",
            "id": "Valley guard Cossack",
            "name": "Valley guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the forest.",
            "id": "Forest guard Cossack",
            "name": "Forest guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the village.",
            "id": "Village guard Cossack",
            "name": "Village guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the garden.",
            "id": "Garden guard Cossack",
            "name": "Garden guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the courtyard.",
            "id": "Courtyard guard Cossack",
            "name": "Courtyard guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the watchman's hut.",
            "id": "Hut guard Cossack",
            "name": "Hut guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the wagon.",
            "id": "Wagon guard Cossack",
            "name": "Wagon guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossak who was a guard of the cup.",
            "id": "Cup guard Cossak",
            "name": "Cup guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossak who was a guard of the saber.",
            "id": "Saber guard Cossak",
            "name": "Saber guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossak who was a guard of the flints.",
            "id": "Flint guard Cossak",
            "name": "Flint guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossak who was a guard of the ruble.",
            "id": "Ruble guard Cossak",
            "name": "Ruble guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossak who was a guard of the horse.",
            "id": "Horse guard Cossak",
            "name": "Horse guard Cossak",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossak",
            "id": "Cossack",
            "name": "Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Hussar who took the cup.",
            "id": "Hussar",
            "name": "Hussar",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Sentinel who paced up and down the bridge.",
            "id": "Sentinel",
            "name": "Sentinel",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Esaul who gave orders.",
            "id": "Esaul",
            "name": "Esaul",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French cavalry unit.",
            "id": "French cavalry",
            "name": "French cavalry",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French infantry unit.",
            "id": "French infantry",
            "name": "French infantry",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French artillery baggage train.",
            "id": "French artillery baggage train",
            "name": "French artillery baggage train",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French convoy of prisoners.",
            "id": "French prisoner convoy",
            "name": "French prisoner convoy",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "French baggage train commanded by Marshal Junot.",
            "id": "Junot's baggage train",
            "name": "Junot's baggage train",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who sharpened the saber under the wagon.",
            "id": "Sharpening Cossack",
            "name": "Sharpening Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who asked for flints.",
            "id": "Flint asking Cossack",
            "name": "Flint asking Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who took the cup.",
            "id": "Cup taking Cossack",
            "name": "Cup taking Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was angry about saddle girths.",
            "id": "Angry Cossack",
            "name": "Angry Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was sleeping under the wagon.",
            "id": "Sleeping Cossack",
            "name": "Sleeping Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard of the watch",
            "id": "Watch guard Cossack",
            "name": "Watch guard Cossack",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Cossack who was a guard",
            "id": "Guard Cossack",
            "name": "C.  ",
            "type": "PERSON"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0736dbb00d27b6d676c3bc0fc7f736d5049ee3e0ce2b419f4fb3be5682c237e4": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "And to feel not exactly dull, but sad?\"\n\n\"I should think so!\" he replied. \"I have felt like that when everything was all",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage depicts a nostalgic conversation among Natasha, Nicholas, and Sonya, philosophical musings on souls, a musical interlude, the arrival of festive mummers, a costume party, and a moonlit sleigh ride to Melyukova's house where the mummers continue their performance.\n- People: Natasha, Nicholas, Sonya, Dimmler, Countess, Count, Petya, Melyukova, Madame Schoss, Zakhar\n- Places: sitting room, drawing room, ballroom, Melyukova's house, old house, porch, Kosoy meadow\n- Events: reminiscence, philosophical discussion, harp performance, singing, mummers' arrival, costume party, sleigh ride, arrival at Melyukova\n- Objects: harp, nocturne, candle, troyka sleigh, horse, costume\n",
        "summary": "Natasha, Nicholas, and Sonya reminisce about childhood, discuss souls, listen to Dimmler play, sing, host mummers in costumes, and ride sleighs to Melyukova's where the festivities continue."
      }
    },
    "0746d3078beb03e4c7c685a6bd7910c3976303dc5eadadc113add827870671d2": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "The battle of Borodino was not fought on a chosen and entrenched position with forces only slightly weaker than those of",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage describes the strategic situation before the Battle of Borodino, Pierre Bezukhov's movements through Mozhaysk and Tatarinova, his encounters with wounded soldiers, a doctor, militia, and officers, his observation of the battlefield layout, and the religious procession culminating in Count Kutuzov's participation in the service.",
        "summary": "Pierre travels from Mozhaysk, sees wounded carts, receives advice from a doctor, watches militia work, surveys the Borodino battlefield, learns positions from an officer, and witnesses a church procession where Kutuzov kneels before an icon."
      }
    },
    "08991c5f48ae3e1391a5c52cb0efd97a21240d392ee9130983484b416c3b46d4": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "The soldiers, for the most part handsome fellows and, as is always the case in an artillery company, a head and shoulder",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage describes Captain Tushin’s experience during a fierce battle, his interactions with superiors and wounded comrades, the chaotic retreat and night camp, and a later debriefing where Russian commanders discuss the action and Tushin’s loss of guns.",
        "summary": "Captain Tushin fights a French attack, retreats under orders, assists wounded cadet Rostov, and later faces questioning by Prince Bagration and Prince Andrew in a command hut."
      }
    },
    "09e8e6aa7934c4a4aa7c28aa67ebcef33deb6cfa2ff0a5b9847942be59b935cd": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "that she was innocent and unhappy at my desertion, and much more. I knew that if I once let myself see her I should not ",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Pierre Bezukhov, husband of Helene Bezukhova, absent‑minded crank, member of a secret order, diary writer.",
            "id": "Pierre Bezukhov",
            "name": "Pierre Bezukhov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Helene Bezukhova, wife of Pierre Bezukhov, prominent salon hostess in Petersburg, attended the Erfurt meeting, praised by Napoleon.",
            "id": "Helene Bezukhova",
            "name": "Helene Bezukhova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Joseph Alexeevich, benefactor and advisor to Pierre Bezukhov, author of letters, appears in Pierre's dreams.",
            "id": "Joseph Alexeevich",
            "name": "Joseph Alexeevich",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Boris Drubetskoy, intimate friend of the Bezukhov household, admitted to the secret order, nominated by Pierre.",
            "id": "Boris Drubetskoy",
            "name": "Boris Drubetskoy",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Napoleon Bonaparte, French emperor who noticed Helene Bezukhova at the Erfurt theater.",
            "id": "Napoleon",
            "name": "Napoleon",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince de Ligne, noble who wrote eight‑page letters to Helene Bezukhova.",
            "id": "Prince de Ligne",
            "name": "Prince de Ligne",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Count Rumyantsev, leader of the French circle of the Napoleonic alliance.",
            "id": "Count Rumyantsev",
            "name": "Count Rumyantsev",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Caulaincourt, member of the French circle of the Napoleonic alliance.",
            "id": "Caulaincourt",
            "name": "Caulaincourt",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bilibin, poet who saved epigrams to present in Countess Bezukhova's presence.",
            "id": "Bilibin",
            "name": "Bilibin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Countess Bezukhova, title of Helene Bezukhova, host of a distinguished salon.",
            "id": "Countess Bezukhova",
            "name": "Countess Bezukhova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Brother V., member of the secret order who advised Pierre Bezukhov.",
            "id": "Brother V.",
            "name": "Brother V.",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Brother A., member of the secret order who appeared in Pierre's dream guiding him.",
            "id": "Brother A.",
            "name": "Brother A.",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Brother O., member of the secret order who visited Pierre and discussed the order.",
            "id": "Brother O.",
            "name": "Brother O.",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Brother G., member of the secret order who visited Pierre.",
            "id": "Brother G.",
            "name": "Brother G.",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Brother Urusov, member of the secret order who talked with Pierre about worldly vanities.",
            "id": "Brother Urusov",
            "name": "Brother Urusov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Grand Master, leader of the secret order.",
            "id": "Grand Master",
            "name": "Grand Master",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Dolokhov, duelist who met Pierre Bezukhov in Moscow after their duel.",
            "id": "Dolokhov",
            "name": "Dolokhov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Nicholas Rostov, younger brother of the Rostov family, serving modestly in an obscure regiment.",
            "id": "Nicholas Rostov",
            "name": "Nicholas Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Vera, young woman who accepted Berg's proposal.",
            "id": "Vera",
            "name": "Vera",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Berg, suitor who proposed to Vera and was accepted.",
            "id": "Berg",
            "name": "Berg",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Old Count, father of the Rostov children, seeking an official post in Petersburg.",
            "id": "Old Count",
            "name": "Old Count",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mitenka, manager of the Rostov estate Otradnoe.",
            "id": "Mitenka",
            "name": "Mitenka",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Peronskaya, maid of honor present at the Rostov gatherings.",
            "id": "Peronskaya",
            "name": "Peronskaya",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French embassy, diplomatic mission whose members attended Helene's salon.",
            "id": "French embassy",
            "name": "French embassy",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "French circle of the Napoleonic alliance, social group in Petersburg.",
            "id": "French circle of the Napoleonic alliance",
            "name": "French circle of the Napoleonic alliance",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Secret Order, a fraternal organization to which Pierre and others belong.",
            "id": "Secret Order",
            "name": "Secret Order",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Helene's salon, gatherings of intellectuals and diplomats hosted by Helene Bezukhova.",
            "id": "Helene's salon",
            "name": "Helene's salon",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Date of Pierre's diary entry on 24 November (year unspecified).",
            "id": "24 November",
            "name": "24 November",
            "type": "DATE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Date of Pierre's diary entry on 27 November (year unspecified).",
            "id": "27 November",
            "name": "27 November",
            "type": "DATE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Date of Pierre's diary entry on 3 December (year unspecified).",
            "id": "3 December",
            "name": "3 December",
            "type": "DATE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Date of Pierre's diary entry on 7 December (year unspecified).",
            "id": "7 December",
            "name": "7 December",
            "type": "DATE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Date of Pierre's diary entry on 9 December (year unspecified).",
            "id": "9 December",
            "name": "9 December",
            "type": "DATE"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0a3daf55cf6940b5d966239d8f3ebae27366c1b9257c46385e6cb07f505baff3": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "Two young citizens were joking with some serf girls who were cracking nuts. All these conversations, especially the joki",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage recounts Petya’s emotional reaction to a cannon firing celebration for peace with the Turks, his desire to join the army, a chaotic biscuit‑throwing incident, his visit to friend Obolenski, Count Ilya Rostov’s assistance, and a massive assembly of nobles and merchants at the Sloboda Palace where debates on conscription, militia, and the Emperor’s manifesto occur, culminating in a resolution to supply soldiers and the Emperor’s entrance speech.",
        "summary": "Petya is inspired by a cannon celebration and the Emperor’s presence, vows to enlist, experiences a biscuit scramble, seeks support from Obolenski and Count Rostov, then attends a grand gathering at Sloboda Palace where Pierre and others debate military reforms, leading to a resolution to provide troops and the Emperor’s address."
      }
    },
    "0a659ec39aaf0b8b219b41774479f8533119cbd15956831e1f5b1e53a9a61786": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "The battle of Borodino was not fought on a chosen and entrenched position with forces only slightly weaker than those of",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "The Battle of Borodino was a major engagement between Russian and French forces during the 1812 campaign.",
            "id": "Battle of Borodino",
            "name": "Battle of Borodino",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Shevardino Redoubt was a fortified position that fell to the French before the Battle of Borodino.",
            "id": "Shevardino Redoubt",
            "name": "Shevardino Redoubt",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Russians were the defending army opposing the French at Borodino.",
            "id": "Russians",
            "name": "Russians",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "The French were the invading army led by Napoleon during the 1812 campaign.",
            "id": "French",
            "name": "French",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Pierre is a Russian nobleman traveling through the battlefield area.",
            "id": "Pierre",
            "name": "Pierre",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mozhaysk is a town north of Moscow where Pierre began his journey.",
            "id": "Mozhaysk",
            "name": "Mozhaysk",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Tatarinova is a location where Russian troops were digging entrenchments.",
            "id": "Tatarinova",
            "name": "Tatarinova",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mikhail Kutuzov was the Russian commander-in-chief during the 1812 campaign.",
            "id": "Mikhail Kutuzov",
            "name": "Mikhail Kutuzov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bennigsen was a Russian general serving under Kutuzov.",
            "id": "Bennigsen",
            "name": "Bennigsen",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Napoleon Bonaparte was the French emperor leading the invasion of Russia.",
            "id": "Napoleon",
            "name": "Napoleon",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Valuevo is a village where Napoleon was stationed before the battle.",
            "id": "Valuevo",
            "name": "Valuevo",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Smolensk highroad is a major road crossing the battlefield area.",
            "id": "Smolensk highroad",
            "name": "Smolensk highroad",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Kolocha Monastery is a monastery whose cross and belfry were visible on the battlefield horizon.",
            "id": "Kolocha Monastery",
            "name": "Kolocha Monastery",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Semenovsk is a burned village visible on the left side of the battlefield.",
            "id": "Semenovsk",
            "name": "Semenovsk",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bezubova is a village shown in the distance beyond the battlefield.",
            "id": "Bezubova",
            "name": "Bezubova",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Zakharino is another village visible beyond the battlefield.",
            "id": "Zakharino",
            "name": "Zakharino",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Kolocha River is a river flowing on the right side of the battlefield.",
            "id": "Kolocha River",
            "name": "Kolocha River",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Moskva River is a river marking the Russian right flank during the battle.",
            "id": "Moskva River",
            "name": "Moskva River",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "The head army doctor is a senior medical officer who advises Pierre.",
            "id": "Head army doctor",
            "name": "Head army doctor",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Smolensk Mother of God icon is a religious image carried by the Russian army.",
            "id": "Smolensk Mother of God icon",
            "name": "Smolensk Mother of God icon",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A white church near Borodino serves as a focal point for the procession.",
            "id": "White church at Borodino",
            "name": "White church at Borodino",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Peasant militiamen are local volunteers working on fortifications.",
            "id": "Peasant militiamen",
            "name": "Peasant militiamen",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A cavalry regiment is a mounted unit that blocks Pierre's carriage.",
            "id": "Cavalry regiment",
            "name": "Cavalry regiment",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Wounded soldiers are injured troops being transported in carts.",
            "id": "Wounded soldiers",
            "name": "Wounded soldiers",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0ab39c9630c30b51eb7028577b656ac720243576ce66926b3cdf6b16c103f486": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "\n\nA few days before his departure a special thanksgiving, at which Nicholas was present, was held in the cathedral for t",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage narrates Nicholas's emotional turmoil surrounding his encounter with Princess Mary, his prayers, the arrival of letters that free him from his engagement to Sonya, subsequent interactions with Mary, Sonya's forced sacrifice, events at Troitsa monastery, and later Pierre's arrest and treatment by guards.",
        "summary": "Nicholas meets Princess Mary, prays for freedom, receives a letter from Sonya releasing him, and navigates complex relationships; later Pierre is arrested and mistreated."
      }
    },
    "0b0d07e1fa738fd5d9b659442ff52d0da81b60081ff7d5d34bc9772f5d0d487e": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "Besides this feeling which absorbed her altogether and hindered her from following the details of her husband's plans, t",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Countess Mary, whose soul strives toward the infinite, the eternal, and the absolute, and feels regret for lacking feeling for her nephew Nicholas.",
            "id": "Countess Mary",
            "name": "Countess Mary",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Nicholas Bolkonski, a young boy, nephew of Countess Mary, who is described as gentle, sensitive, and whose feelings are compared to those of his aunt.",
            "id": "Nicholas Bolkonski",
            "name": "Nicholas Bolkonski",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Pierre, husband of Natasha, who engages in philosophical discussions and dreams of leading an army with young Nicholas.",
            "id": "Pierre",
            "name": "Pierre",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Natasha, wife of Pierre, who converses with him in a way that defies logical rules and expresses deep love for him.",
            "id": "Natasha",
            "name": "Natasha",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince Sergey, described by Pierre as a fine fellow and clever.",
            "id": "Prince Sergey",
            "name": "Prince Sergey",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Platon Karataev, a figure referenced by Pierre and Natasha as someone whose approval they wonder about.",
            "id": "Platon Karataev",
            "name": "Platon Karataev",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mitya, a child mentioned by Natasha as naughty, likened to his father.",
            "id": "Mitya",
            "name": "Mitya",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau, philosopher whose works are read by Nicholas.",
            "id": "Rousseau",
            "name": "Rousseau",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Montesquieu, philosopher whose works are read by Nicholas.",
            "id": "Montesquieu",
            "name": "Montesquieu",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Sismondi, author whose works are read by Nicholas.",
            "id": "Sismondi",
            "name": "Sismondi",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Dessalles, caretaker who sleeps on four pillows and is described as good and kind by Nicholas.",
            "id": "Dessalles",
            "name": "Dessalles",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince Andrew, father of Nicholas who appears in Nicholas's dream, caressing and pitying him.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew",
            "name": "Prince Andrew",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Arakcheev, authority who gives Nicholas orders in his dream.",
            "id": "Arakcheev",
            "name": "Arakcheev",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mucius Scaevola, historical figure referenced by Nicholas as an example of self‑sacrifice.",
            "id": "Mucius Scaevola",
            "name": "Mucius Scaevola",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Plutarch, author whose works are visualized by Nicholas in his dream.",
            "id": "Plutarch",
            "name": "Plutarch",
            "type": "PERSON"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0b2881aa5499b2eff5fb43b9f4e736b007a5648c1061f9d3a8828052fb731363": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "\n\n\"What orders, your excellency?\" said the huntsman in his deep bass, deep as a proto-deacon's and hoarse with hallooing",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Nicholas, a member of the Rostov family, participates in the hunt.",
            "id": "Nicholas_Rostov",
            "name": "Nicholas Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Daniel is a huntsman who speaks in a deep bass voice.",
            "id": "Daniel",
            "name": "Daniel",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Uvarka is sent by Nicholas to listen and reports on the she-wolf.",
            "id": "Uvarka",
            "name": "Uvarka",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Milka is a dog that Nicholas scratches behind the ears.",
            "id": "Milka",
            "name": "Milka",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Natasha is a young lady eager to join the hunt.",
            "id": "Natasha",
            "name": "Natasha",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Petya is a young man who shouts encouragement for the hunt.",
            "id": "Petya",
            "name": "Petya",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Michael is a huntsman mentioned by Natasha.",
            "id": "Michael",
            "name": "Michael",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Uncle is a distant relative of the Rostovs, a man of small means.",
            "id": "Uncle",
            "name": "Uncle",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "The old count, father of Nicholas, leads the hunting party.",
            "id": "Count_Ilya_Rostov",
            "name": "Count Ilya Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Simon is the personal attendant of Count Ilya Rostov.",
            "id": "Simon_Chekmar",
            "name": "Simon Chekmar",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mitka is a groom serving Count Ilya Rostov.",
            "id": "Mitka",
            "name": "Mitka",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Nastasya Ivanovna is a buffoon who dresses in a woman's cloak.",
            "id": "Nastasya_Ivanovna",
            "name": "Nastasya Ivanovna",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Karay is a shaggy old dog known for tackling a big wolf.",
            "id": "Karay",
            "name": "Karay",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Trunila is a harrier hound favored by Natasha.",
            "id": "Trunila",
            "name": "Trunila",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Viflyanka is a sorrel gelding owned by Count Ilya Rostov.",
            "id": "Viflyanka",
            "name": "Viflyanka",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Donets is a chestnut horse ridden by Nicholas Rostov.",
            "id": "Donets",
            "name": "Donets",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Arabchik is a black horse ridden by Natasha.",
            "id": "Arabchik",
            "name": "Arabchik",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Otradnoe is a copse/enclosure where the she-wolf and cubs moved.",
            "id": "Otradnoe",
            "name": "Otradnoe",
            "type": "PLACE"
          },
          {
            "description": "An old wolf encountered during the hunt.",
            "id": "Wolf",
            "name": "Wolf",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "The deity to whom Nicholas prays.",
            "id": "God",
            "name": "God",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "The fifteenth of September when the old count prepared to go out.",
            "id": "September_15",
            "name": "September 15",
            "type": "DATE"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0be6150059a62c65858e4587bb5b8906135a8bd860256a1e32854d82659020b1": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "Suddenly the wolf's whole physiognomy changed: she shuddered, seeing what she had probably never seen before--human eyes",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Count Rostov, the old count who participated in the hunt.",
            "id": "Count Rostov",
            "name": "Count Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Nicholas, a young count and participant in the chase.",
            "id": "Nicholas",
            "name": "Nicholas",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Count Ilagin, a rival noble involved in the hunt.",
            "id": "Count Ilagin",
            "name": "Count Ilagin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Daniel, a man who seized the wolf with a dagger.",
            "id": "Daniel",
            "name": "Daniel",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Natasha, sister of Nicholas who attended the hunt.",
            "id": "Natasha",
            "name": "Natasha",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Petya, brother of Natasha who attended the hunt.",
            "id": "Petya",
            "name": "Petya",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Uncle, a relative of Nicholas who rode with him.",
            "id": "Uncle",
            "name": "Uncle",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Wolf, the old wolf pursued by the hunters and dogs.",
            "id": "Wolf",
            "name": "Wolf",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Karay, an old borzoi dog that tried to seize the wolf.",
            "id": "Karay",
            "name": "Karay",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Milka, a black‑spotted borzoi belonging to Nicholas.",
            "id": "Milka",
            "name": "Milka",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Lyubim, a reddish borzoi that rushed at the wolf.",
            "id": "Lyubim",
            "name": "Lyubim",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Erza, a red‑spotted female borzoi owned by Ilagin.",
            "id": "Erza",
            "name": "Erza",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Rugay, a black‑spotted borzoi owned by Nicholas.",
            "id": "Rugay",
            "name": "Rugay",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Red fox, a short‑legged fox chased by the borzois.",
            "id": "Red fox",
            "name": "Red fox",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Hare, a swift hare that became the focus of the chase.",
            "id": "Hare",
            "name": "Hare",
            "type": "ANIMAL"
          },
          {
            "description": "Wood, the forest area where the wolf could escape.",
            "id": "Wood",
            "name": "Wood",
            "type": "PLACE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Ravine, a thickly overgrown ravine where hounds were released.",
            "id": "Ravine",
            "name": "Ravine",
            "type": "PLACE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Ilagin's upland, a mile‑away field owned by Ilagin used for hunting.",
            "id": "Ilagin's upland",
            "name": "Ilagin's upland",
            "type": "PLACE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Winter rye field, the field of winter rye where the hare was sighted.",
            "id": "Winter rye field",
            "name": "Winter rye field",
            "type": "PLACE"
          },
          {
            "description": "Stubble, the area of stubble near the hare's flight.",
            "id": "Stubble",
            "name": "Stubble",
            "type": "PLACE"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0c0f51ab9990b78eb17732fa1749973989f052b8e66110eef8a6499181bcd9ad": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "It is wonderful how clever I am and how...  charming she is,\" she went on, speaking of herself in the third person, and ",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Young woman attending her first grand ball, daughter of Count and Countess Rostov.",
            "id": "Natasha Rostova",
            "name": "Natasha Rostova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Natasha's sister, helping with dressing for the ball.",
            "id": "Sonya Rostova",
            "name": "Sonya Rostova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Father of Natasha and Sonya, attended the ball wearing a blue swallow-tail coat.",
            "id": "Count Rostov",
            "name": "Count Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mother of Natasha and Sonya, wore a claret-colored velvet dress at the ball.",
            "id": "Countess Rostova",
            "name": "Countess Rostova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Thin maid of honor, friend of the countess, accompanied the Rostovs to the ball.",
            "id": "Marya Ignatevna Peronskaya",
            "name": "Marya Ignatevna Peronskaya",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Maid who put out the candle and later helped Natasha with her dress.",
            "id": "Dunyasha",
            "name": "Dunyasha",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Maid who assisted in shortening Natasha's gauze dress.",
            "id": "Mavra",
            "name": "Mavra",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Man called aside by the countess earlier in the story.",
            "id": "Boris",
            "name": "Boris",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince Andrew Bolkonski, a younger man in a white uniform recognized by Natasha.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew Bolkonski",
            "name": "Prince Andrew Bolkonski",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Handsome officer of the Horse Guards, brother of Countess Bezukhova.",
            "id": "Anatole Kuragin",
            "name": "Anatole Kuragin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Stout man referred to as a buffoon by Peronskaya, likely Pierre Bezukhov.",
            "id": "Pierre",
            "name": "Pierre",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Countess Bezukhova, called the Queen of Petersburg.",
            "id": "Helene",
            "name": "Helene",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Hostess who greeted arrivals at the ball, also known as Marya Antonovna Naryshkina.",
            "id": "Marya Antonovna Naryshkina",
            "name": "Marya Antonovna Naryshkina",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Emperor present at the New Year's Eve ball.",
            "id": "Emperor",
            "name": "Emperor",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French ambassador Caulaincourt mentioned at the ball.",
            "id": "French ambassador Caulaincourt",
            "name": "French ambassador Caulaincourt",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Dutch ambassador with gray hair mentioned at the ball.",
            "id": "Dutch ambassador",
            "name": "Dutch ambassador",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Old grandee of Catherine's day who hosted the ball and midnight supper.",
            "id": "Old grandee",
            "name": "Old grandee",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Mansion on the English Quay where the ball was held.",
            "id": "English Quay",
            "name": "English Quay",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Gardens where Peronskaya was to be called at ten o'clock.",
            "id": "Taurida Gardens",
            "name": "Taurida Gardens",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "New Year's Eve ball attended by the Rostov family and society.",
            "id": "New Year's Eve Ball",
            "name": "New Year's Eve Ball",
            "type": "EVENT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Date of the ball: 31 December 1809.",
            "id": "1809-12-31",
            "name": "1809-12-31",
            "type": "DATE"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0c266d2163b75d43c90858d4fda9be2a816b8c0ed232b143d6c204bf15a24674": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "\n\n\"When are you starting?\" he asked.\n\n\"Oh, don't speak of his going, don't! I won't hear it spoken of,\" said the princes",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Prince Andrew, husband of Lise and friend of Pierre.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew",
            "name": "Prince Andrew",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Princess Lise, wife of Prince Andrew, pregnant and fearful.",
            "id": "Lise",
            "name": "Lise",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Pierre, friend of Prince Andrew, present at the dinner.",
            "id": "Pierre",
            "name": "Pierre",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince Vasili Kuragin, father of Anatole Kuragin.",
            "id": "Prince Vasili Kuragin",
            "name": "Prince Vasili Kuragin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Anatole Kuragin, son of Prince Vasili, host of the gambling party.",
            "id": "Anatole Kuragin",
            "name": "Anatole Kuragin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Dolokhov, officer, gambler and duelist, present at Anatole's party.",
            "id": "Dolokhov",
            "name": "Dolokhov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Stevens, English naval officer involved in a drinking bet.",
            "id": "Stevens",
            "name": "Stevens",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bonaparte, referenced by Prince Andrew in a comparison.",
            "id": "Bonaparte",
            "name": "Bonaparte",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Anna Pavlovna, mentioned as a social setting.",
            "id": "Anna Pavlovna",
            "name": "Anna Pavlovna",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "The war that Prince Andrew is going to.",
            "id": "War",
            "name": "War",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Marriage, discussed by Prince Andrew as undesirable.",
            "id": "Marriage",
            "name": "Marriage",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Pregnancy of Lise, hinted at in the dialogue.",
            "id": "Pregnancy",
            "name": "Pregnancy",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Elegant newly decorated dining room where dinner occurs.",
            "id": "Dining Room",
            "name": "Dining Room",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Drawing room mentioned earlier in the conversation.",
            "id": "Drawing Room",
            "name": "Drawing Room",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Location near which Anatole's house stands, the Horse Guards Barracks.",
            "id": "Horse Guards Barracks",
            "name": "Horse Guards Barracks",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Anatole Kuragin's house where the party takes place.",
            "id": "Kuragin House",
            "name": "Kuragin House",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "0d2c01ca1e2c49711f05266dcd3a2534763eeb9a050f746435fa4f9e9fcdb2c6": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "\"\n\nAnd the countess bent over her reticule to hide her agitated face. Sonya embraced Natasha and kissed her.\n\nNatasha lo",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage narrates the Rostov family's departure from Moscow, Natasha's excited recognition of Pierre Bezukhov in a coachman's disguise, Pierre's subsequent stay at Bazdeev's house sorting manuscripts and preparing for battle, and the broader military movements of Kutuzov's retreat and Napoleon's observation of Moscow from Poklonny Hill.",
        "summary": "Rostovs leave Moscow; Natasha spots Pierre; Pierre handles Bazdeev's books and seeks a pistol; Kutuzov orders retreat; Napoleon surveys Moscow."
      }
    },
    "0e140fefc7730a9a97267d79cefa2d9251d0cf236235949373c7e2be2c1475e4": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "But all this was only talk; in reality (though the Council of Fili, at which it was decided to abandon Moscow, had not y",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "This chunk narrates the Rostov family's frantic preparations to abandon Moscow in late August 1812, detailing their daily activities, emotional states, and interactions with wounded officers amid the looming battle. It includes scenes of packing, the countess’s fears, Natasha’s initiative to shelter the wounded, and the broader social turmoil in Moscow on its final day before surrender.",
        "summary": "The Rostovs scramble to pack and flee Moscow in August 1812, with Natasha helping wounded officers, while the city descends into chaos and prepares for battle."
      }
    },
    "0e3f83e7c855499c6ac275093378cb1c89e23c9bf6d7c71ee145c36f8473e010": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "\n\nPrince Bagration looked at Tushin, evidently reluctant to show distrust in Bolkonski's emphatic opinion yet not feelin",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage alternates between a wartime scene with Prince Bagration, Tushin, Rostov, and the aftermath of a French attack, then shifts to Book Three (1805) focusing on Prince Vasili's manipulations of Pierre Bezukhov, his social ascent, and detailed interactions at Anna Pavlovna's gatherings, especially involving Helene.",
        "summary": "A battlefield episode ends with Bagration's troops rejoining Kutuzov, followed by Prince Vasili scheming to advance Pierre Bezukhov's career and social standing, culminating in a winter 1805-6 soirée hosted by Anna Pavlovna."
      }
    },
    "0f737e4a55fb5db11ed7407fc2608e2ee121265e8424f3c9cd22a6079d6bc1f2": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "But the Austrian general, continuing to read, frowned angrily and jerked his elbows, as if to say: \"You can tell me your",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Austrian general who participated in the council of war.",
            "id": "Langeron",
            "name": "Langeron",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian general present at the council of war.",
            "id": "Miloradovich",
            "name": "Miloradovich",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "General Weyrother, author of the military plan under discussion.",
            "id": "Weyrother",
            "name": "Weyrother",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Officer Przebyszewski who held his hand to his ear toward Weyrother.",
            "id": "Przebyszewski",
            "name": "Przebyszewski",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Officer Dohkturov, a little man who studied the map.",
            "id": "Dohkturov",
            "name": "Dohkturov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian commander Kutuzov, senior officer at the council.",
            "id": "Kutuzov",
            "name": "Kutuzov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince Andrew, Russian noble who reflects on death and glory.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew",
            "name": "Prince Andrew",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince Dolgorukov, Russian officer who claimed the French had retreated.",
            "id": "Dolgorukov",
            "name": "Dolgorukov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Count Ilya Rostov's son, a hussar on skirmishing duty.",
            "id": "Rostov",
            "name": "Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Prince Bagration, Russian commander whose detachment includes Rostov.",
            "id": "Bagration",
            "name": "Bagration",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Sergeant Fedchenko, hussar sergeant who rode with Rostov.",
            "id": "Fedchenko",
            "name": "Fedchenko",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Tit, the old cook serving Kutuzov.",
            "id": "Tit",
            "name": "Tit",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Nesvitski, officer sharing a hut with Prince Andrew.",
            "id": "Nesvitski",
            "name": "Nesvitski",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Russian Emperor referenced in the narrative.",
            "id": "Emperor",
            "name": "Emperor",
            "type": "PERSON"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "110d84539d0c0fab0184158ece48e0f411309e88326907bccc0f1b92fab7e96d": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "Among the men who very soon became frequent visitors at the Rostovs' house in Petersburg were Boris, Pierre whom the cou",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Berg is a Livonian gentleman, officer who was a captain in the Guards in 1809, decorated for Austerlitz and the Finnish war, and suitor of Vera Rostova.",
            "id": "Berg",
            "name": "Berg",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Count Rostov is the father of Vera and Natasha, an old count facing financial difficulties.",
            "id": "Count Rostov",
            "name": "Count Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Countess Rostova is the mother of Vera and Natasha, often referred to as the old countess.",
            "id": "Countess Rostova",
            "name": "Countess Rostova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Vera Rostova is the eldest daughter, a twenty‑four‑year‑old countess, and the object of Berg's marriage proposal.",
            "id": "Vera Rostova",
            "name": "Vera Rostova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Natasha Rostova is the younger daughter, sixteen years old in 1809, formerly engaged to Boris.",
            "id": "Natasha Rostova",
            "name": "Natasha Rostova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Sonya Rostova is Natasha's sister.",
            "id": "Sonya Rostova",
            "name": "Sonya Rostova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Boris is an army officer who left Moscow in 1805, visited the Rostovs, and was formerly engaged to Natasha.",
            "id": "Boris",
            "name": "Boris",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Pierre is a visitor who, with Boris and Berg, became a frequent guest at the Rostovs' house in Petersburg.",
            "id": "Pierre",
            "name": "Pierre",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Countess Bezukhova is a noblewoman whose intimacy gave Boris a brilliant position in society.",
            "id": "Countess Bezukhova",
            "name": "Countess Bezukhova",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Austerlitz is the 1805 battle where Berg was wounded and earned two decorations.",
            "id": "Austerlitz",
            "name": "Austerlitz",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Finnish war is the conflict in which Berg distinguished himself and earned two decorations.",
            "id": "Finnish war",
            "name": "Finnish war",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "The Guards is the elite military unit where Berg held the rank of captain in 1809.",
            "id": "Guards",
            "name": "Guards",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Petersburg is the city where the Rostovs' house is located and where Berg holds lucrative posts.",
            "id": "Petersburg",
            "name": "Petersburg",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Moscow is the city Boris left in 1805 to join the army and where he had previously visited the Rostovs.",
            "id": "Moscow",
            "name": "Moscow",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Livonia is the region of Berg's obscure gentleman family.",
            "id": "Livonia",
            "name": "Livonia",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "The year 1809, when Natasha is sixteen and Berg is a captain.",
            "id": "1809",
            "name": "1809",
            "type": "DATE"
          },
          {
            "description": "The year 1805, when Boris left Moscow and the battle of Austerlitz occurred.",
            "id": "1805",
            "name": "1805",
            "type": "DATE"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "11ed6119a46313f40aef8dd2014a397d7c3520241945bacb9ff036bc80473be0": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "* I shall certainly adopt an innovation and call him simply Bonaparte!\"\n\n\n    * \"We must let him off the u!\"\n\n\n\"But joki",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Russian prince and soldier, main protagonist of the narrative.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew Bolkonski",
            "name": "Prince Andrew Bolkonski",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Host who leads the diplomatic set called les notres.",
            "id": "Bilibin",
            "name": "Bilibin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Secretary to the embassy and member of the diplomatic set les notres.",
            "id": "Prince Hippolyte Kuragin",
            "name": "Prince Hippolyte Kuragin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Austrian emperor who gave audience to Prince Andrew.",
            "id": "Emperor Francis",
            "name": "Emperor Francis",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Austrian minister of war who congratulated Prince Andrew.",
            "id": "Minister of War",
            "name": "Minister of War",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Officers of the Austrian army present at the levee.",
            "id": "Austrian officers",
            "name": "Austrian officers",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "French marshal who participated in the Thabor Bridge operation.",
            "id": "Murat",
            "name": "Murat",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French marshal who participated in the Thabor Bridge operation.",
            "id": "Lannes",
            "name": "Lannes",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French marshal who participated in the Thabor Bridge operation.",
            "id": "Belliard",
            "name": "Belliard",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Austrian officer defending the Thabor Bridge.",
            "id": "Prince Auersperg von Mautern",
            "name": "Prince Auersperg von Mautern",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bilibin's man who helped move luggage.",
            "id": "Franz",
            "name": "Franz",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian commander mentioned as receiving the Grand Cross of Maria Theresa.",
            "id": "Kutuzov",
            "name": "Kutuzov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "A military honor awarded by Emperor Francis.",
            "id": "Maria Theresa Order (third grade)",
            "name": "Maria Theresa Order (third grade)",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "A high military award given to Kutuzov.",
            "id": "Grand Cross of Maria Theresa",
            "name": "Grand Cross of Maria Theresa",
            "type": "CONCEPT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Diplomatic set led by Bilibin, consisting mainly of diplomats.",
            "id": "les notres",
            "name": "les notres",
            "type": "ORGANIZATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Town where Bilibin's house is located.",
            "id": "Brunn",
            "name": "Brunn",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Capital city mentioned in the narrative.",
            "id": "Vienna",
            "name": "Vienna",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Descriptive term for the location of Brunn.",
            "id": "Moravian hole",
            "name": "Moravian hole",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "River near the Thabor Bridge.",
            "id": "Danube",
            "name": "Danube",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Bridge over the Danube that was crossed by French marshals.",
            "id": "Thabor Bridge",
            "name": "Thabor Bridge",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Place where the battle began.",
            "id": "Durrenstein",
            "name": "Durrenstein",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Location referenced in distance measurement.",
            "id": "Krems",
            "name": "Krems",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Town mentioned as a possible destination.",
            "id": "Olmutz",
            "name": "Olmutz",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Military engagement discussed by Prince Andrew.",
            "id": "the battle",
            "name": "the battle",
            "type": "EVENT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Formal gathering where Prince Andrew stood among Austrian officers.",
            "id": "the levee",
            "name": "the levee",
            "type": "EVENT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Meeting between Prince Andrew and Emperor Francis.",
            "id": "the audience with Emperor Francis",
            "name": "the audience with Emperor Francis",
            "type": "EVENT"
          },
          {
            "description": "Incident where French marshals crossed the mined Thabor Bridge.",
            "id": "Thabor Bridge affair",
            "name": "Thabor Bridge affair",
            "type": "EVENT"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "122089633d169340a64ef7a4ab7623c5b19ecea8bdd5279b6bb485fd1d511bcb": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "\"I always said he was the only man capable of defeating Napoleon.\"\n\nBut next day no news arrived from the army and the p",
      "schema_name": "SummarizedContent",
      "response": {
        "description": "The passage recounts a series of events during the 1812 French invasion of Russia, focusing on the Russian court’s anxiety over the lack of news, the death of Countess Helene Bezukhova, the abandonment and burning of Moscow, and the reactions of key figures such as the Emperor, Prince Vasili, Kutuzov, and Colonel Michaud. It then shifts to Nicholas Rostov’s journey to Voronezh to procure horses, describing his interactions with local officials and society.",
        "summary": "The Russian court reacts to the abandonment of Moscow and the death of Countess Bezukhova, with the Emperor confronting Colonel Michaud about the loss. Later, Nicholas Rostov travels to Voronezh to buy remounts, experiencing provincial hospitality."
      }
    },
    "1249ada45095b8e221472bdb3284d50aee711d525378c5995930060a5b8797f3": {
      "method": "structured_output",
      "user_input_preview": "On the narrow Augesd Dam where for so many years the old miller had been accustomed to sit in his tasseled cap peacefull",
      "schema_name": "KnowledgeGraph",
      "response": {
        "nodes": [
          {
            "description": "Narrow dam where the battle and chaotic crowd scene took place.",
            "id": "Augesd Dam",
            "name": "Augesd Dam",
            "type": "LOCATION"
          },
          {
            "description": "Miller who habitually sat in a tasseled cap on the dam.",
            "id": "Old Miller",
            "name": "Old Miller",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Grandson of the old miller who handled a silvery fish in a watering can.",
            "id": "Grandson",
            "name": "Grandson",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Group of Moravians in shaggy caps and blue jackets who drove two‑horse carts loaded with wheat over the dam.",
            "id": "Moravians",
            "name": "Moravians",
            "type": "GROUP"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian officer, now an officer, wounded in the arm during the battle.",
            "id": "Dolokhov",
            "name": "Dolokhov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Regimental commander who rode on horseback during the crowd at the dam.",
            "id": "Regimental Commander",
            "name": "Regimental Commander",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "General who fell from his horse after a cannonball struck near the dam.",
            "id": "General",
            "name": "General",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "French Emperor who directed the battle and visited the wounded Prince Andrew.",
            "id": "Napoleon",
            "name": "Napoleon",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian prince wounded on the Pratzen Heights, later captured.",
            "id": "Prince Andrew Bolkonski",
            "name": "Prince Andrew Bolkonski",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian officer of the Emperor Alexander's Horse Guards, identified as a prisoner.",
            "id": "Prince Repnin",
            "name": "Prince Repnin",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Young lieutenant of the Horse Guards, also a prisoner.",
            "id": "Lieutenant Sukhtelen",
            "name": "Lieutenant Sukhtelen",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Napoleon's chief surgeon who examined the wounded prisoners.",
            "id": "Larrey",
            "name": "Larrey",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Russian officer who returned home on leave in early 1806.",
            "id": "Nicholas Rostov",
            "name": "Nicholas Rostov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Companion of Nicholas Rostov who traveled with him to Moscow.",
            "id": "Denisov",
            "name": "Denisov",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Footman who recognized Nicholas Rostov upon his arrival home.",
            "id": "Prokofy",
            "name": "Prokofy",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Old Michael, a servant asleep on a chest in the house.",
            "id": "Old Michael",
            "name": "Old Michael",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Rostov's sister who gave him a gold icon to wear around his neck.",
            "id": "Princess Mary",
            "name": "Princess Mary",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Rostov's mother who greeted him at the house entrance.",
            "id": "Rostov Mother",
            "name": "Rostov Mother",
            "type": "PERSON"
          },
          {
            "description": "Family member who embraced Nicholas Rostov on his return.",
            "id": "Sonya",
            "name": "Sonya",
